wpsitecare.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy for WP Site Care | WP Site Care

This Privacy Policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in U.S. privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience. We will store this information for as long as needed or when it is asked to be removed by the individual themselves.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, open a Support Ticket, enter information on our site, and when you provide us with feedback on our products or services.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (email or phone inquiries)

**How do we protect your information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular malware scanning services.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing or billing purposes, you may opt-out at any time by writing to or emailing us via the contact us page
  * You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
  * If you believe that any information we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to, call or email us as soon as possible at the phone number or address detailed at the bottom of this page. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s help instructions to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to receive assistance over the telephone by contacting customer service.

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google Advertising**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles and reviewed on Google website (https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en). They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

**We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.**

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared.

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy page.

You can change your personal information:

  * By emailing us
  * By calling us

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?  
**  
It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

  * We will notify you via email within 7 business days
  * We will notify you via letter within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**International Users**

If you are accessing the Site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use, which is governed by the law of the United States and this Privacy Policy, you will be transferring your personal information into the United States and you consent to that transfer.

**Third-Party Services**

We utilize third parties and their platforms or services to power and support the Site, including the following (collectively, “ **Third-Party Services** ”):

  * For hosting, Amazon Web Services.
  * For analytics, to monitor how the Site is being used and to identify potential issues, Mixpanel, Intercom, and Google Analytics.

The Third-Party Services and your provision of information to and storage of your data with such services are subject to their applicable terms and policies.

**CAN-SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
  * Send information and updates pertaining to work orders.
  * Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at support@southernweb.com or follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Southern Web, LLC  
3565 Piedmont Road, NE  
Building Four, Suite 360  
Atlanta, Georgia 30305  
United States  
404-848-9440

* * *

**Last Updated:** July 16, 2018
